{
    "subject": "resource/Tegan_and_Sara",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Sire_Records_artists",
    "human_readable": "Tegan and Sara are about Sire Records artists.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7294060587882996,
            "question": "Who are Tegan and Sara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6691840887069702,
            "question": "Are Tegan and Sara associated with any record labels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6262840032577515,
            "question": "What other artists are signed to Sire Records?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5523084998130798,
            "question": "Where are Tegan and Sara from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5313814282417297,
            "question": "Which music genre are Tegan and Sara known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5104259848594666,
            "question": "What is Sire Records known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34193316102027893,
            "question": "What instruments do Tegan and Sara play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33165955543518066,
            "question": "What are some of Tegan and Sara's most popular songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30297181010246277,
            "question": "When did Tegan and Sara start their music career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3006425201892853,
            "question": "Has Tegan and Sara won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tegan and Sara are about Sire Records artists.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5551_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Tegan and Sara start their music career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5551_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Tegan and Sara's most popular songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5551_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments do Tegan and Sara play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5551_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5551_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents contain information that supports the triple, specifically mention that Tegan and Sara released The Con on Sire Records."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Tegan and Sara signed with Sire Records, which is a subsidiary of Warner Music Group. Later, they returned to their roots by signing with Mom+Pop Music, founded by Michael Goldstone who originally signed them to Sire Records. This information supports the statement that Tegan and Sara are artists associated with Sire Records."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}